(Mike:)In space,
you couldn't even toss me a pen,
(Mike:)and that was in zero gravity.
(Howard:)Okay, thanks for the pep talk.
(Mike:)Anytime, Froot Loops.
(Mike:)Give your wife a hug for me.
(Mike:)She's so much cuter than you, I
don't know how you ever got her.
(Skype blips off)
(Bernadette:)He's so nice.
(Penny:)Hey, sorry about that.
(Amy:)No, we're sorry.
(Amy:)We never should have been
comparing relationships
(Amy:)in the first place.
(Sheldon:)Why? We won.
(Sheldon:)You know, I say, next, we take
on Koothrappali and his dog.
(Sheldon:)Really give
ourselves a challenge.
(Leonard:)I just want to say
one more thing about this.
(Leonard:)Just because Penny
and I are very different people
(Leonard:)does not mean
that we're a bad couple.
(Sheldon:)The answer is
one simple test away.
(Sheldon:)Hmm? You know,
it's like
(Sheldon:)when I thought there was
a possum in my closet.
(Sheldon:)Did I sit around
wondering?
(Sheldon:)No, I sent Leonard in with
a pointy stick and a bag.
(Leonard:)I killed
his Chewbacca slippers.